

□ (+380) 67-513-3259 | wov.dorosh@gmail.com | osQverful | ovolodymyr-dorosh

Summary.

Bachelor of Computer Science and Software Engineer at Symphony Solutions. Practice learner that interested in challenging tasks and learning new technologies or tools that could be applied in practice and bring effective value for community. A former experienced Software Salesperson that found passion in web development and headed to gain Master's degree in the University of Waterloo in order to become an expert as Software Craftsman.

## **Education**

## Lviv Polytechnic National University

Lviv, Ukraine

**BACHELOR OF COMPUTER SCIENCE** 

Sep. 2017 - Aug. 2021

Cumulative Average: 81.15%.

• Organizing committee member of 15th CADSM International Conference.

## Ternopil Gymnasium named after Ivan Franko

Ternopil, Ukraine

Sep. 2011 - May. 2017

SECONDARY SCHOOL GRADUATE

Cumulative Average: 10.4 / 12 (86%).

• Honors: Government Silver Medal for high academic achievements.

# Skills\_

Frameworks/Technologies Java, HTML/CSS, LaTeX, Spring Framework, PostgreSQL, Microservices, ActiveMQ/Kafka, Flyway, Keycloak.

Languages Advanced in English, Intermediate in Polish, Elementary Proficiency in French, Fluent in Ukrainian. **Interests** Software Engineering, Running Marathons, Playing Guitar, Music Distribution, Visual Communications.

# Work Experience \_

**Symphony Solutions** 

Lviv, Ukraine

Dec. 2021 - Present

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

- Development of an urban mobility solution for public transport. Java Spring applications as microservices architecture, deployed as K8S
- Proposed and implemented solution for role-based security based on Spring Security with documentation for further management.
- Introduced and developed a new microservice integrated with Flowable BPMN engine.
- Implemented internal money wallet with transaction logging and REST API.
- REST API development: from OAS definition to covering implemented logic by unit and e2e tests.
- · Knowledge sharing assistance for new on-boarded engineers regarding project architecture, GitLab pipelines, development approach
- Active participation in dev-talks and architecture discussions.

Lviv, Ukraine Etiya Inc.

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER May. 2021 - Dec. 2021

- Development and maintenance of software applications designed for Telecom Industry in Canada.
- Deep down investigation, identifying the root causes of problems and resolving.
- Managing integration processes within different IT systems.

Webitel Lviv, Ukraine

SALES MANAGER

Feb. 2019 - Dec. 2020

- Providing Customer Center and CRM solutions for CIS, Europe and US regions. Products line: Creatio CRM, Webitel IP-PBX.
- Achieved good personal reputation in partners network that led to receiving inbound leads from recommendations.
- Managed and made a sale with company from Fortune 500 list.
- Development of sales kit and strategies: presentations, key advantages, proof of concept, individual presentations, project road-maps.
- Representing company and lead generation at conferences: Terrasoft Accelerate Global Conference, Bank Online MFO Summit in Kyiv.

## Honors & Awards

2021	<b>5th Place</b> , Race Nation 21km - obstacle races.	Bukovel, Ukraine
2021	Participant Award Medal, 6th Molokiya Lviv Half Marathon.	Lviv, Ukraine
2017	Silver Medal, for academic achievements in Ternopil Gymnasium named after I. Franko.	Ternopil, Ukraine
2017	<b>Certificate of Appreciation</b> , for the active participation in public and social work of the Ternopil Gymnasium named after I. Franko.	Ternopil, Ukraine
2014	<b>Certificate of Appreciation and 2nd Place</b> , for active participation in the literary contest based on Dante's poem "The Divine Comedy" at Ternopil Gymnasium named after I. Franko.	Ternopil, Ukraine
2012	<b>1st Place</b> , championship in general physical training of rowing department on kayaks and canoes.	Ternopil, Ukraine
2013	<b>Certificate of Appreciation</b> , for academic achievements and participation in academic concert at Music College named after S. Krushelnytska.	Ternopil, Ukraine
2012	<b>Certificate of Appreciation</b> , for academic achievements and participation in academic concert at Music College named after S. Krushelnytska.	Ternopil, Ukraine
2010	<b>Certificate of Appreciation</b> , for academic achievements and participation in academic concert at Music College named after S. Krushelnytska.	Ternopil, Ukraine
2010	Certificate of Appreciation, for high academic achievements in Ternopil Primary School #35.	Ternopil, Ukraine

# **Scholarly and Professional Activities**

## **EPAM Systems (Java Laboratory)**

Lviv, Ukraine

**STUDENT** Nov. 2020 - May. 2021

- Gained theoretical knowledge about OOP, GRASP/SOLID principles and practical skills with Java Core, JUnit, Mockito, JDBC, H2.
- Developed personal web-project that helps in managing tests & questionnaires. Developed on Servlets and JSP pages, without frameworks, published on my github account.
- Refactored personal web-project from Java Servlets into Spring application with REST API endpoints.

## **CAD Department of Lviv Polytechnic**

Lviv, Ukraine Sep. 2020

CONSULTANT

• Assisted in creating new curriculum subject "Methods of Business Communications".

- Shared my Sales Management commercial experience and recommended literature with professors.
- Prepared curriculum practicum tasks as laboratory works.

# 15th CADSM Conference by CAD Department of Lviv Polytechnic

Lviv, Ukraine

## MEMBER OF ORGANIZING COMMITTEE

Sep. 2019 - Dec. 2019

- Created an Instagram account @cadsm\_conference.
- Developed and managed content, grew audience.
- Gathered e-mail list of potential interested universities for the marketing campaign.

## **Ternopil Without Problems Hackaton**

Ternopil, Ukraine

PARTICIPANT

May. 2018

- Co-creator of the concept of "AR Reproduction of the Destroyed Historical Architectural Heritage" in order to solve the problem of tourism in Ternopil.
- Presentation and speech composer, represented team and solution in front of the audience.